ixfu.com 2011-12-31

# ixfu - PC games download

ixfu Privacy Policy

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for ixfu.com. You can reach us with questions regarding this statement via the [contact page](http://www.ixfu.com/contactus.php).

Your IP address is used only when you become a member as a backup identification tool for polls and other member services. 

Our sites use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites, and for other purposes. These cookies are used soley for the sites, and the content contained is not distributed to third parties. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and e-mail address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information related to ixfu.com only when requested by said user. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Your e-mail address will never be given or sold to a third party and will only be viewed by ixfu. Your mobile device e-mail address not be disclosed and will only be used for sending breaking news upon request. Other information you use will only be used to collect broad demographic information about our visitors. 

This site contains links to other sites. ixfu is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

### Third Party Advertising

We could use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our sites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

### Public Forums

Our sites make message boards available free to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about our users. Staff overlook server access daily to ensure the above holds true. 

### Children's Guidelines

This site gives children between the ages of 13 and 18 the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. Please take proper measures if you do not wish your child to have access to public forums and message boards. As always, exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in a public forum. 

In order to comply with the COPPA ruling, if you are younger than 13 years of age, you are forbidden from becoming a member of ixfu or posting information on ixfu message boards without direct parental consent. You may have your parent or guardian contact us to verify that you have been granted permission to use this site. 

### Newsletter and Information Removal

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database, deciding to stop receiving our future communications or change their frequency: 

  1. You can [contact us](http://www.ixfu.com/contactus.php)
  2. You can edit your preferences via the ixfu.com main page, Account Information

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, you can reach us via the [contact page](http://www.ixfu.com/contactus.php).
